Guide to the Lee P. Brown Papers, 1954-2013 MS 509
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Houston Police Department Chief, 1982-1990, 42734
  - Subseries D: Speeches, 213225
    - Texas Peace Officers Association Awards Banquet, 1982-08-20; 214605 (Box 30, Folder 83)
    - Houston Urban Bankers Association, 1982-08-24; 214606 (Box 30, Folder 84)
    - Houston School District Area I Educational Specialists, 1982-08-26; 214607 (Box 30, Folder 85)
    - Men's Day Observance - Trinity East United Methodist Church, 1982-08-29; 214608 (Box 30, Folder 86)
    - National Black Police Association Conference, 1982-08-30; 214609 (Box 30, Folder 87)
    - Congregation Beth Israel, 1982-09-07; 214610 (Box 30, Folder 88)
    - Session of the Texas Annual Conference of the African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1982-09-22; 214611 (Box 30, Folder 89)
    - Southwest Science Forum Symposium on Violence and Aggression, 1982-10-04; 214612 (Box 30, Folder 90)
    - Prepared for James K. Stewart at the First National Conference on Repeat Offenders, 1982-10-06; 214613 (Box 30, Folder 91)
    - International Association of Women Police, 1982-10-08; 214614 (Box 30, Folder 92)
    - Association of Black Social Workers State Conference, 1982-10-09; 214615 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - "To Be Followers of Christ: A Challenge for the 80's", 1982-10-10; 214616 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Wesley United Methodist Church Men's Program, 1982-10-10; 214617 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - "Citizen Complaint Processing", 1982-10-16; 214618 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - "Police Use of Deadly Force", 1982-10-16; 214619 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Antioch Missionary Baptist Church, 1982-10-22; 214620 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "Parents Against Drugs", 1982-10-23; 214621 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - S.A. Pleasants Elementary School, 1982-11-09; 214622 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Windsor Village United Methodist Church, 1982-11-09; 214623 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police, 1982-11-10; 214624 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - "Policing in Houston", 1982-11-10; 214625 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - American Magazine Conference, 1982-10-27; 214626 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - The Advisory Board of the National Institute of Justice, 1982-11-15; 214627 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Butler Street YMCA - Hungry Club Forum, 1982-11-17; 214628 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Houston Independent School District - "Parents Calling Parents" Workshop, 1982-11-23; 214629 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - High School for Law Enforcement and Criminal Justice "Close-Up" Program, 1982-12-01; 214630 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - The Houstonian Forum Break, 1982-12-08; 214631 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Notes, ca. 1982; 214632 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Reception Honoring Lee P. Brown, ca. 1982; 214633 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Urban League, ca. 1982; 214634 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - "White Collar Crime: The Atlanta Response", ca. 1982; 214635 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - 47th Annual Meeting and Installation Dinner - Houston Citizens Chamber of Commerce, 1983-01-28; 214636 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Houston Airport Optimist Club Meeting, 1983-01-31; 214637 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - River Oaks Country Club Breakfast Club, 1982-02-02; 214638 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Garden of Gethsemane Baptist Church, 1983-02-06; 214639 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Veterans' Administration Black History Program, 1983-02-08; 214640 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Zollie Scales Retirement Banquet, 1983-02-11; 214641 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Association of Black Social Workers of Texas, 1983-02-12; 214642 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Black History Celebration - Mount Olive Baptist Church, 1983-02-13; 214643 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - NAACP Fundraising Banquet, 1983-02-14; 214644 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1983-02-15; 214645 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Prairie View A&M University, 1983-02-16; 214646 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Settegast Community Health Center, 1983-02-18; 214647 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Conference on Criminal Justice and Racial Minorities - State of Washington Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1983-03-05; 214648 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Police/Citizens Positive Interaction Program In-Service Training, 1983-03-10; 214649 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - American Baptist Northeast District Association, 1983-03-11; 214650 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Wesley Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Lay Organization, 1983-03-13; 214651 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - "Building a Partnership between Police and Community", 1983-03-19; 214652 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Regional Employee Assistance Forum, 1983-03-23; 214653 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - City of Houston Consular Corps Briefing, 1983-03-24; 214654 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Houston Baptist Pastors and Ministers Fellowship Fourth Annual Awareness Banquet, 1983-03-25; 214766 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Contemporary Christian Church - Fourth Annual Founder's Day, 1983-04-10; 214767 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Angelina County Citizens Chamber of Commerce, 1983-04-12; 214768 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - High School for Law Enforcement and Criminal Justice Dedication, 1983-04-12; 214769 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Greater Ward Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1983-04-17; 214770 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Remarks to the Texas Legislature - Amendements to Article 1269M, 1983-04-19; 214771 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Masonic Banquet Statewide Convention, 1983-04-23; 214772 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Clinton Park United Methodist Church Family and Friend Day, 1983-04-24; 214773 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - San Jacinto College Spring Commencement, 1983-05-06; 214774 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - The MacNeil-Lehrer Report Transcript #1987, 1983-05-10; 214775 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Inroads/Houston, Inc., 1983-05-13; 214778 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Police Awards Ceremony, 1983-05-17; 214779 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - California State University - Fresno Commencement, 1983-05-21; 214780 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Barbara Jordan High School Commencement, 1983-05-22; 214781 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - National Conference on Social Welfare, 1983-05-23; 214782 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - Jerusalem Baptist Church Annual Banquet, 1983-05-25; 214783 (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - Moses Le Roy Ring Ceremony, 1983-05-27; 214784 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - "There Is Always an Alternative", 1983-05; 214785 (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayor's Annual Meeting, 1983-06-14; 214786 (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - Episcopal Church of the Resurrection Men's Day, 1983-06-19; 214787 (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Jerusalem Missionary Baptist Church Annual Nineteenth of June Celebration, 1983-06-19; 214788 (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - National Organization of Black Law Enforcement Executives Conference, 1983-06-21; 214789 (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - Galilee Missionary Baptist Church Men's Day Service, 1983-06-26; 214790 (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Texas Department of Community Affairs Children and Youth Services Division Workshop, 1983-07-14; 214791 (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Christian Faith Missionary Baptist Church, 1983-07-15; 214792 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Issues that Impact on the Community and Quality of Life - University of Oklahoma, 1983-07-22; 214793 (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - National Urban League Conference, 1983-08-02; 214794 (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - Kiwanis Club of Houston, 1983-08-24; 214795 (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - Community-Police Partnerships: New Challenges for the 80's, 1983-08-27; 214796 (Box 31, Folder 69)
    - "Fear of Crime Touches All of Us", 1983-08-27; 214797 (Box 31, Folder 70)
    - "The Atlanta Experience: It's Impact on Law Enforcement and the Community", 1983-09-02; 214798 (Box 31, Folder 71)
    - Oregon Police Academy Graduation, 1983-09-02; 214799 (Box 31, Folder 72)
    - Sloan Memorial United Methodist Church, 1983-09-11; 214800 (Box 31, Folder 73)
    - Willowridge Missionary Baptist Church Community Awareness Day, 1983-09-18; 214801 (Box 31, Folder 74)
    - Sunlight Missionary Baptist Church, 1983-11-20; 214802 (Box 31, Folder 75)
    - "What is the Importance of Acquiring a Higher Education?" - Yale Street Missionary Baptist Church, 1983-11-27; 214803 (Box 31, Folder 76)
    - Greater Houston Close-Up Program, 1983-12-05; 214804 (Box 31, Folder 77)
    - Speech materials, 1983-1987; 214805 (Box 31, Folder 78)
    - Black History Month, ca. 1983; 214806 (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Cub Scouts, ca. 1983; 214807 (Box 31, Folder 80)
    - Houston Ministers Against Crime, ca. 1983; 214808 (Box 31, Folder 81)
    - Information Age - The Information Society, ca. 1983; 214809 (Box 31, Folder 82)
    - "Let Not Our Living Be in Vain", 1984-01-13; 214810 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - City Wide Interdenominational Get Acquainted Family and Friends Day, 1984-01-29; 214811 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - The Spaulding for Children Adoption Agency, 1984-02-12; 214812 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Mount Vernon United Methodist Church, 1984-02-12; 214813 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - John F. Kennedy Elementary School, 1984-02-14; 214814 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - "What Will Your Legacy Be?" - Sloan Memorial United Methodist Church, 1984-02-19; 214815 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Black History Month - Greatest First Baptist Church, 1984-02-19; 214816 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Black History Month - Mt. Zion Baptist Church, 1984-02-19; 214817 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Internal Revenue Service, 1984-02-22; 214818 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Houston Gardens Elementary School, 1984-02-25; 214819 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Black History Month - Missionary Nazarene Baptist Church, 1984-02-26; 214820 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Union of Black Studewnts - University Of Houston - Clear Lake, 1984-02-29; 214821 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Casper Wyoming College - Social Sciences Seminar - "1984", 1984-03-02; 214822 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - McNamara Elementary School, 1984-03-12; 214823 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - National Association of Blacks in Criminal Justice, 1984-03-28; 214824 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Martin Luther King Community Center 16th Anniversary, 1984-04-05; 214825 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Nu Boule Membership, 1984-04-15; 214826 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Bastion Elementary School, 1984-04-18; 214827 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Ancient Arabic Nobles of the Mystic Shrine, 1984-04-21; 214828 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Texas Southern University Honor Awards Program, 1984-04-26; 214829 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Texas Association of Tonsorial Artists, 1984-05-07; 214830 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Jack Yates High School - Spring Sports Banquet, 1984-05-08; 214859 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Houston Police Department Annual Awards Ceremony, 1984-05-15; 214860 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Kashmere Senior High School Commencement, 1984-05-19; 214861 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Forest Brook High School Commencement, 1984-05-31; 214862 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - National Association of Social Workers - Black Homicide Workshop, 1984-06-14; 214863 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - "Fear Reduction Strategies" - The Texas Police Association, 1984-06-19; 214864 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Wilbeforce University's 1984 National Alumni Conference, 1984-07-19; 214865 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - National United Church Ushers Association of America, 1984-07-27; 214866 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - National Conference of State Trial Judges, 1984-08-04; 214867 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - FBI National Academy Graduation, 1984-09-14; 214870 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Grace Presbyterian Church Banquet, 1984-10-02; 214871 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - National Association of Police Planners, 1984-10-12; 214872 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - National Association of Blacks in Criminal Justice Conference, 1984-11-10; 214873 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - National Conference on Crime, 1984-12-03; 214874 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - The Justice George Lewis Ruffin Society, 1984-12-05; 214875 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Productivity speech, 1984; 214876 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - John Marshall Middle School, ca. 1984; 214877 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - "Transcending Race", ca. 1984; 214878 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Conference on Terrorism, 1985-02-01; 214879 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Black History Month - Veteran's Administration, 1985-02-08; 214880 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Jordan Grove Missionary Baptist Church, 1985-02-10; 214881 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - 1st Annual Afro-American Cultural Affair, 1985-02-13; 214882 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - The Black Portfolio 1st Annual Awards Banquet, 1985-02-23; 214883 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - First Christian Church/Temple Beth Israel Annual Brotherhood Dinner, 1985-2-26; 214884 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Texas Southern University Alumni Association, 1985-03-01; 214885 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Just Say No to Drugs Conference, 1985-03-02; 214886 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - First Mount Olive Baptist Church, 1985-03-03; 214887 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Houston Achievement Place Annual Dinner, 1985-03-05; 214888 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Preschool Fingerprint Workshop, 1985-04-10; 214889 (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Laws Memorial Church of God in Christ Fellowship Banquet, 1985-06-22; 214890 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - 1st Annual Afro American Police Officers Awards Banquet, 1985-04-25 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Portland Urban League Annual Dinner, 1985-05-16 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Jefferson Davis High School - Law Day, 1985-04-26 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Police Week Awards Ceremony, 1985-05-21 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Awards Program for School Bus Drivers, 1985-05-24 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Morning Star Baptist Church's Annual Graduation Service, 1985-05-26 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Ship of Zion Baptist Church's Boy's Club, 1985-06-09 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - John Jay College Graduation Ceremony, 1985-05-31 (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Funeral Services for Assistant Chief R. G. McKeehan, 1985-06-19 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - National Association of Black Narcotics Agents, 1985-06-21 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Progressive New Hope Baptist Church Men's Day Program, 1985-06-23; 214891 (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - U.M.W. Scottish Rite Grand Lodge Banquet, 1985-06-27; 214892 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Vietnamese Community of Houston Awards, 1985-07-07; 214893 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Christian Methodist Episcopal Church Conference, 1985-07-17; 214894 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Texas Peace Officers Association, 1985-08-19; 214895 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - National Black Police Association Education and Training Conference, 1985-08-28; 214896 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Western Region Boule - Sigma Pi Phi Fraternity, 1985-09-21; 214897 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Police Stress - Texas Southern University, 1985-10-08; 214898 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Gulf Coast Community Services Association Roast and Toast Dinner, 1985-10-23; 214899 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Governing Urban Texas in the Next Decade - The University of Texas at Arlington, 1985-10-24; 214900 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Barbados Conference, 1985-11-04; 214901 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Ethnic Minority Conference, 1985-11-23; 214902 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity - Founders Day Observance, 1985-12-01; 214903 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Ebenezer Baptist Church, 1985-12-01; 214904 (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - St. Paul's African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1985-12-08; 214905 (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Waco Conference of Christians and Jews, 1985-12-12; 214906 (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Fear Reduction Crime Program, ca. 1985; 214907 (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Speech materials, 1985-1988; 214908 (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - The Houston Police Department: An Update, 1986-02-04; 214909 (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Social Security Teleservice Center, 1986-02-18; 214910 (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Texas Southern Central Churches of God in Christ, 1986-02-22; 214911 (Box 32, Folder 82)
    - Nazarene Missionary Baptist Church, 1986-02-23; 214912 (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - "Construction Crime Prevention" - Greater Houston Builders Association, 1986-02-25; 215170 (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - Salem Missionary Baptist Church Ushers Banquet, 1986-03-01; 215171 (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - NAACP Southwest Region Annual Leadership Training Conference, 1986-03-08; 215172 (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Willing Workers Baptist Church Banquet, 1986-03-15; 215173 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - "What Is Occurring in Contemporary Society?", 1986-03-18; 215174 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - San Franscisco Police Officers Association, 1986-04-19; 215175 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Chamber of Commerce Crime Control Committee, 1986-04-24; 215176 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - "Telecommunications and the Houston Police Department" - Houston Space and Telecom Trade Symposium, 1986-04-28; 215177 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - National Forum of the Eisenhower Foundation, 1986-05-02; 215178 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Alvin Police Officers Association, 1986-05-10; 215179 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - "Today's Student, Tomorrow's Decision Maker" - Teens Oriented Police Seminar, 1986-05-10; 215180 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - NAACP - Dona Ana Branch, 1986-05-17; 215181 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - "Just Say No" Banquet, 1986-05-21; 215182 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Booker T. Washington Senior High School Graduation, 1986-05-22; 215183 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Contemporary Learning Center, 1986-06-02; 215184 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Corporate Volunteer Council of Greater Houston, 1986-06-19; 215185 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Prairie View A&M University - Cooperative Extension Program Youth Awards Luncheon, 1986-06-20; 215186 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Loyal Missionary Baptist Church, 1986-06-22; 215187 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Briarchase Missionary Baptist Church Banquet, 1986-07-11; 215188 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Second Baptist Church, 1986-08-03; 215189 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - "Collaborative Efforts of Law Enforcement and Health Professionals to Decrease Violence and Crime in the Black Community", 1986-08-07; 215190 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Greater Anderson Memorial Church of God in Christ, 1986-08-10; 215191 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Troop 99 Eagle Court of Honor, 1986-08-10; 215192 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Texas Peace Officers Association, 1986-08-11; 215195 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Police Academy Graduation Ceremony, 1986-09-13; 215196 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Basic Speech for Civic Associations and Business Groups, 1986-09-26; 215197 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Payne Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1986-10-11; 215198 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Southwest Community of Schools, 1986-10-15; 215199 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Payne Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1986-10-19; 215201 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Trinity Garden Church of Christ, 1986-10-23; 215202 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Houston Child Guidance Center, 1986-11-02; 215203 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - "The Impact of Crime on Victims: What Can Be Done", 1986-11-11; 215204 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Conference on Terrorism and Corporate America, 1986-11-17; 215205 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Mayor's Drug Awareness Day Luncheon, 1986-11-18; 215208 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Conference on Terrorism and Corporate America, 1986-11; 215210 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Safety Council Greater Houston, 1986-12-16; 215211 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Speech Material - Supervision, 1986; 215212 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - "The Chief and the Community", ca. 1986; 215214 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - "Crack House Problem in Houston", ca. 1986; 215215 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Eisenhower Foundation, ca. 1986; 215216 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Ministers Advisory Council - Drugs, ca. 1986; 215218 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - National Organization of Black Law Enforcement, ca. 1986; 215219 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - "Reducing the Fear of Crime", ca. 1986; 215221 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - "Violence in America Homicides Involving Minorities", ca. 1986; 215225 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - "Achievements of Black People" - Texas Eastern Toastmasters, 1987-01-15; 215226 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Houston Ministers Against Crime, 1987-02-07; 215228 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - "View from the Front of the Bus: Progress Blacks Have Made in Law Enforcement Since 1960", 1987-02-17; 215229 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Houston Area Rehabilitation Association - Annual Spring Conference, 1987-02-18; 215230 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Houston Ministers Against Crime, 1987-02-19; 215251 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Integrated Missionary Baptist Church - Black History Celebration, 1987-02-23; 215252 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - "Hometown Proud - Houston Proud" - Cub Scout Pack, 1987-02-27; 215253 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Minority Health Seminar - Prairie View A&M Nurses, 1987-02-28; 215254 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - The Association of Labor Management Administrators and Consultants on Alcoholism, 1987-03-10; 215255 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - National Coalition of Black Meeting Planners, 1987-03-21; 215256 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Summit on Crime in the Black Community, 1987-03-28; 215257 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Pro Random Drug Testing, 1987-03; 215258 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - "Houston Police Department Reponse/Work in Crisis Intervention" - The Community Education Conference on Domestic Violence, 1987-04-10; 215259 (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - The African Methodist Episcopal Church's Texas Conference Lay Organization Workshop, 1987-04-11; 215260 (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Purchasing Management Association of Houston, 1987-04-14; 215261 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Benefit Banquet Honoring Galveston Precinct Five Constable Sonny James, 1987-04-15; 215424 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Barbara Jordan High School for Careers Graduation, 1987-05-09; 215425 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Westbury Senior High School Graduation, 1987-05-10; 215426 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - "Policing in City of Houston, Texas" - Eisenhower Foundation, 1987-05; 215435 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Crack Houston Problem in Houston, 1987-06-23; 215436 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Houston Chapter of the National Federation of the Blind, 1987-07-24; 215437 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - "Opening Remarks Command Staff Retreat", 1987-07; 215438 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - HPD Response to Alcohol and Drug Induced Violence, 1987-08-20; 215439 (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Annual Meeting of National Police Chiefs Association, 1987-09-16; 215440 (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - "An Ounce of Prevention: Eliminating Self-Destructive Behaviors", 1987-10-22; 215441 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Panel Discussion AIDS, 1987-11-18; 215442 (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - "The Importance of Young Adults Continuing Their Education", 1987-12-05; 215443 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Congress of National Black Churches, 1987-12-09; 215444 (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - "Follow Through Evangelism" - Lyons Missionary Baptist Church, 1987-12-18; 215445 (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Martin Luther King Day, ca. 1987; 215446 (Box 33, Folder 71)
    - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Commemorative Program, 1988-01-17; 215447 (Box 33, Folder 72)
    - Friendship Baptist Church, 1988-01-17; 215448 (Box 33, Folder 73)
    - Downtown YMCA Sustaining Campaign, 1988-01-19; 215449 (Box 33, Folder 74)
    - Black Youth - Fifth National Policy Institute, 1988-01-22; 215450 (Box 33, Folder 75)
    - "The Problems of Adolescents with Drugs", 1988-01-26; 215451 (Box 33, Folder 76)
    - "The 80's and Beyond: Our Christian Challenge" - Wesley Chapel African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1988-02-06; 215452 (Box 33, Folder 77)
    - Southeast Texas Black Historical Society, 1988-02-16; 215453 (Box 33, Folder 78)
    - "Black Officers in Our History: Problems, Privileges, and Responsibilities", 1988-02-21; 215454 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Black Police Officers Awards Ceremony, 1988-02-25; 215455 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Houston Chapter National Forum for Black Public Administrators Banquet, 1988-03-10; 215456 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Jones Memorial United Methodist Church, 1988-03-12; 215457 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Hermann Life Flight - Eleventh Annual Emergency Car Symposium, 1988-03-15; 215458 (Box 34, Folder 5)